<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    // License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        &lt;i>For more information about the project: &lt;br>
        https://github.com/scoute-dich/HHSMoodle&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.
    </string>


    // Help Dialogs

    <string name="hhs_help1">HHS Moodle</string>
    <string name="hhs_help_text1">This is the Browser shows you our school Moodle platform.</string>

    <string name="hhs_help2">Functionality</string>
    <string name="hhs_help_text2">You can save every website as a bookmark or share it. If you click on the star, your bookmarks
        will be shown. Just try all the menu entries.</string>


    <string name="bookmark_help1">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_help_text1">Here all your saved bookmarks are shown. If you click on the star the bookmark will be saved
        as your favorite and will load, when you open the browser.</string>

    <string name="bookmark_help2">Menus</string>
    <string name="bookmark_help_text2">Check the menu (also the toolbar), change the icons. A long click on an entry will also open
        a menu.</string>


    <string name="todo_help1">Todo list</string>
    <string name="todo_help_text1">Click on an entry to open it. Click on the exclamation mark and you will get a notification in
        your statusbar. You can also change the priority of an entry. A long click opens a menu.</string>

    <string name="todo_help2">The list</string>
    <string name="todo_help_text2">A short click will delete the entry, with a long click you can edit it.</string>


    <string name="note_help1">Notes</string>
    <string name="note_help_text1">Here you can create notes with attachments.</string>

    <string name="note_help2">Practically</string>
    <string name="note_help_text2">You can also receive text from other apps to create a note. A short click on an entry will
        open the note, a long click will open (as always) a menu.</string>


    <string name="schedule_help1">Schedule</string>
    <string name="schedule_help_text1">Here you can edit your schedule. Click on an entry to see all todo entries or notes for a
        subject.</string>

    <string name="schedule_help2">A long click …</string>
    <string name="schedule_help_text2">… opens here also a menu.</string>






    <string name="helpSettings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="helpSettings_text">
        &lt;b>Login:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        If your moodle username or password gets changed, you must change this also in the here. Otherwise the app can not
        connect you to our Moodle site.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Security:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Here you can set a pin to protect the app against unwanted access. If you forget it, you can delete all personal
        settings (login, bookmarks, notes, …). You can backup your bookmarks and notes on the sd-card, and restore them
        later.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        All other settings are self explanatory. If you have problems, you can write a mail (\"Contact?\").
    </string>

    <string name="helpGrade_title">Grade calculation</string>
    <string name="helpGrade_text">
        Moodle always calculates in percentage (0-100%). Grades are always in condition to this scala. If you set the maximal credits
        to 100 you can see this scala. Moodle always calculates with the percent scale, not with the grades.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Maximal credits:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Here you can set the maximal credits for a test. The scored credits (middle column) will be set in relation to the maximal
        reachable credits in percent (left column). In the right column you can see the calculated grade.
    </string>

    <string name="helpCourse_text">

        &lt;b>Create list:&lt;/b>&lt;br>

        &#8226;&lt;i> Create text file:&lt;/i> Create one text file per course. In every line you can write a name. The filename
        should be the course name (e.G..: Course 6a).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Copy to phone:&lt;/i> Copy the text file in the \"HHS_Moodle\" folder on your sd-card.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Load file:&lt;/i> Click on the orange button. In the opening dialog you can choose the copied file.
        A new list entry will be created. Then you can delete the text file.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        If you click on a list entry you can create a note, you can open a menu to edit the list entry.
    </string>

    <string name="perm_notShow_title">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary">Only for Android Marshmallow and above: Grant used permission by
        opening \"Permissions\" in the next window. After that restart the app.</string>

    <string name="perm_notShow_title_dist">Do not disturb</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary_dist">Only for Android Nougat and above: Grant used permission
        in the next window, to bring your phone in silent mode during lessons.</string>

</resources>