<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    //License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Used open source library:&lt;br>
        NotificationNotes&lt;br>
        https://github.com/khuttun/NotificationNotes&lt;/i>
    </string>


    //Changelog Dialog

    <string name="changelog_text">
        &lt;i>For more informations visit the project site on github:&lt;br>
        https://github.com/scoute-dich/HHSMoodle&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>v 1.0:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226; first release
    </string>


    //Help Dialogs

    <string name="firstSearch_title">Saving bookmarks</string>
    <string name="firstSearch_title_summary">Show again: Saving bookmarks?</string>
    <string name="firstSearch_text">
        To save a bookmark simply click the icon at the toolbar.
        If you clicked the icon a popup appears. You can now edit the title of the bookmark.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        You can switch back to the main screen or to your favorite (look into the settings) by clicking the toolbar.
        To go back to the main screen you can also press the arrow at the toolbar. Swipe down to reload the website.</string>

    <string name="firstBrowser_title">Browser</string>
    <string name="firstBrowser_title_summary">Show again: Functionality of the browser?</string>
    <string name="firstBrowser_text">
        HHS Moodle is shown in this webview. A webview displays websites in an app. If you have no internet
        connection they will be loaded offline from the cache (this works not o course overviews). If you want to be logged automatically, you must set your username
        and your password in the settings.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        In the webview there is a context menu, which opens on long pressing a link or image.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        You can switch back to the main screen or to your favorite (look into the settings) by clicking the toolbar.
        To go back to the main screen you can also press the arrow at the toolbar. Swipe down to reload the website.</string>

    <string name="firstBookmark_title">Main screen</string>
    <string name="firstBookmark_title_summary">Show again: Tip about the main screen?</string>
    <string name="firstBookmark_text">
        &lt;i>The tabs:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        In the left tab you can open your personal Moodle sites. In the right tab you can see your bookmarks.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Edit bookmarks:&lt;/i>&lt;br>

        Long click on a bookmark opens a popup menu. You can set your favorite bookmark
        (It can be loaded on app start or on title bar click - look in the settings.), edit the title of the bookmark or
        delete it (at least one bookmark is needed).</string>

    <string name="firstScreenshot_title">Making screenshots</string>
    <string name="firstScreenshot_title_summary">Show again: Taking screenshots?</string>
    <string name="firstScreenshot_text">
        You can make screenshots of the whole website (even of the part which is outside of your display.
        Before taking the screenshot wait until the website is fully loaded, to ensure that the whole website is captured.</string>

    <string name="firstNote_title">Taking notes</string>
    <string name="firstNote_title_summary">Show again: Taking notes?</string>
    <string name="firstNote_text">
        &lt;i>Create notes:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        You can make notes if you click the \"Taking note\" entry in the menu or the pencil icon in the toolbar.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Working with notes:&lt;/i>&lt;br>

        Clicking a list entry opens the note. Long click on an entry opens a popup menu. You can edit title and content of the
        note or delete the note (at least one note is needed).&lt;br>
        You can also set a notification to the system status bar. A new screen for editing notifications will open.
        The notification will appear again after a reboot.</string>

    <string name="perm_notShow_title">Permission dialog</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary">Show again: Permission dialog?</string>

</resources>