<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    // License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        &lt;i>For more information about the project: &lt;br>
        https://github.com/scoute-dich/HHSMoodle&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.
    </string>


    // Help Dialogs

    <string name="hhs_help1">HHS Moodle</string>
    <string name="hhs_help_text1">This is the Browser shows you our school Moodle platform.</string>

    <string name="hhs_help2">Functionality</string>
    <string name="hhs_help_text2">You can save every website as a bookmark or share it. If you click on the star, your bookmarks
        will be shown. Just try all the menu entries.</string>


    <string name="bookmark_help1">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_help_text1">Here all your saved bookmarks are shown. If you click on the star the bookmark will be saved
        as your favorite and will load, when you open the browser.</string>

    <string name="bookmark_help2">Menus</string>
    <string name="bookmark_help_text2">Check the menu (also the toolbar), change the icons. A long click on an entry will also open
        a menu.</string>


    <string name="todo_help1">Todo list</string>
    <string name="todo_help_text1">Click on an entry to open it. Click on the exclamation mark and you will get a notification in
        your statusbar. You can also change the priority of an entry. A long click opens a menu.</string>

    <string name="todo_help2">The list</string>
    <string name="todo_help_text2">A short click will delete the entry, with a long click you can edit it.</string>


    <string name="note_help1">Notes</string>
    <string name="note_help_text1">Here you can create notes with attachments.</string>

    <string name="note_help2">Practically</string>
    <string name="note_help_text2">You can also receive text from other apps to create a note. A short click on an entry will
        open the note, a long click will open (as always) a menu.</string>


    <string name="schedule_help1">Schedule</string>
    <string name="schedule_help_text1">Here you can edit your schedule. Click on an entry to see all todo entries or notes for a
        subject.</string>

    <string name="schedule_help2">A long click …</string>
    <string name="schedule_help_text2">… opens here also a menu.</string>


    <string name="random_help1">Random generator</string>
    <string name="random_help_text1">You can just roll a dice (\"dice icon\") or choose somebody randomly from a list.</string>

    <string name="random_help2">Create a list</string>
    <string name="random_help_text2">You can create a list on your own, or import from the course list.</string>


    <string name="grade_help1">Grade calculation</string>
    <string name="grade_help_text1">Moodle calculates grades in percentage. It uses the percentage of the maximum reachable
        points.</string>

    <string name="grade_help2">Grade table</string>
    <string name="grade_help_text2">Enter the maximum of reachable points. Then you can see your grade ant the percentage of the
        reachable points.</string>


    <string name="course_help1">Course lists</string>
    <string name="course_help_text1">From a course list you can create a random or a todo list. All members of the list are in
        the new generated list.</string>

    <string name="course_help2">Import list</string>
    <string name="course_help_text2">Copy a text file in the \"HHS_Moodle-Folder\" of your sd-card. In every line should be the
        name of a member of the new course list.</string>


    <string name="subject_help1">Subject list</string>
    <string name="subject_help_text1">The subject list is mainly used to edit the schedule.</string>

    <string name="subject_help2">Practical</string>
    <string name="subject_help_text2">Just try also here a short or a long press on a list entry.</string>


    <string name="settings_help1">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_help_text1">Here you can change your login data, if they are not actual.
        You can also change the behavior of the app.</string>

    <string name="settings_help2">Security</string>
    <string name="settings_help_text2">It is highly recommended to protect the app with a pin against unwanted access.</string>


    <string name="perm_notShow_title">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary">Only for Android Marshmallow and above: Grant used permission by
        opening \"Permissions\" in the next window. After that restart the app.</string>

    <string name="perm_notShow_title_dist">Do not disturb</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary_dist">Only for Android Nougat and above: Grant used permission
        in the next window, to bring your phone in silent mode during lessons.</string>

</resources>