<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    // License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        &lt;i>For more information about the project: &lt;br>
        https://github.com/scoute-dich/HHSMoodle&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Used open source projects:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>android-file-chooser&lt;br>
        https://github.com/hedzr/android-file-chooser&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>browser&lt;br>
        https://github.com/yoshihiroando/browser&lt;br>&lt;br>

        encrypted-userprefs&lt;br>
        https://github.com/sveinungkb/encrypted-userprefs&lt;br>&lt;br>

        MaterialDesignIcons&lt;br>
        https://github.com/Templarian/MaterialDesign&lt;/i>
    </string>


    // Help Dialogs

    <string name="helpToDo_text">
        Here you can create and edit todo lists.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>The List:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        If you click on a list entry the will open in a new window. If you long click a list entry a popup
        menu opens. You can change the entry icon by clicking on it.  If you click on the \"exclamation mark\" icon, you
        can create a notification which will be restored after a reboot.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Popup menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Edit title:&lt;/i> You can edit the title of the bookmark.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Share list:&lt;/i> You can share the note with every app which is able to receive text
        (SMS, Email,…).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note:&lt;/i> The title of the bookmark will be used as title for a new note, the url for the content.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create calendar entry:&lt;/i> The name of the bookmark will be used as title for a new calendar
        entry. Editing of this entry will take place in your calendar app.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Delete bookmark:&lt;/i> At least one bookmark must remain. All others can be deleted.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note (pen icon):&lt;/i> A new dialog where you can create a new note will open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Sort (list icon):&lt;/i> Different possibilities to sort the list.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open app directory:&lt;/i> You can open, share, rename und delete files.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Tools:&lt;/i> you can choose between calculate grades, random number generator and course lists.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create shortcut:&lt;/i> To have a faster access to the main functions of the app, you can create
        shortcuts on your homescreen (calendar -> offline, My Moodle, bookmarks, notes, create new note).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app. It is highly
        recommended to protect the app with a password against unwanted access.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Help:&lt;/i> Opens the help dialog.
    </string>


    <string name="helpBookmarks_text">
        Here your saved bookmarks are shown.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>The List:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        If you click on a list entry the bookmark opens in the intern browser. If you long click a list entry a popup
        menu opens. You can change the bookmark icon by clicking on it.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Popup menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Edit title:&lt;/i> You can edit the title of the bookmark.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Set as favorite:&lt;/i> If you set a bookmark as favorite, you can open it at the app start or by
        clicking on the toolbar. You can configure that in the settings.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note:&lt;/i> The title of the bookmark will be used as title for a new note, the url for the content.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create todo list:&lt;/i> The title of the bookmark will be used as title for a new todo list, the url for the content.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create shortcut:&lt;/i> A shortcut to the bookmark will be created on your homescreen.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create calendar entry:&lt;/i> The name of the bookmark will be used as title for a new calendar
        entry. Editing of this entry will take place in your calendar app.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Delete bookmark:&lt;/i> At least one bookmark must remain. All others can be deleted.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note (pen icon):&lt;/i> A new dialog where you can create a new note will open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Sort (list icon):&lt;/i> Different possibilities to sort the list.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open app directory:&lt;/i> You can open, share, rename und delete files.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Tools:&lt;/i> you can choose between calculate grades, random number generator and course lists.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create shortcut:&lt;/i> To have a faster access to the main functions of the app, you can create
        shortcuts on your homescreen (calendar -> offline, My Moodle, bookmarks, notes, create new note).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app. It is highly
        recommended to protect the app with a password against unwanted access.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Help:&lt;/i> Opens the help dialog.
    </string>


    <string name="helpNotes_text">
        Here your notes are shown. You can create a note, by clicking the menu entry (pen icon).&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>The list:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        If you click on a list entry the note opens in a dialog. If you long click a list entry a popup
        menu opens. If you click on the circle on the left of a list entry, You can edit the priority of the note.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Popup menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Edit note:&lt;/i> A new dialog, where you can edit priority, title and content of the note, will
        open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Share note:&lt;/i> You can share the note with every app which is able to receive text
        (SMS, Email,…).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create todo list:&lt;/i> The title of the bookmark will be used as title for a new todo list, the url for the content.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create calendar entry:&lt;/i> The name of the note will be used as title for a new calendar
        entry. Editing of this entry will take place in your calendar app.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Delete note:&lt;/i> At least one note must remain. All others can be deleted.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note (pen icon):&lt;/i> A new dialog where you can create a new note will open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Sort (list icon):&lt;/i> Different possibilities to sort the list.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open app directory:&lt;/i> You can open, share, rename und delete files.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Tools:&lt;/i> you can choose between calculate grades, random number generator and course lists.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create shortcut:&lt;/i> To have a faster access to the main functions of the app, you can create
        shortcuts on your homescreen (calendar -> offline, My Moodle, bookmarks, notes, create new note).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app. It is highly
        recommended to protect the app with a password against unwanted access.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Help:&lt;/i> Opens the help dialog.
    </string>


    <string name="helpSettings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="helpSettings_text">
        &lt;b>Login:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        If your moodle username or password gets changed, you must change this also in the here. Otherwise the app can not
        connect you to our Moodle site.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Security:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Here you can set a pin to protect the app against unwanted access. If you forget it, you can delete all personal
        settings (login, bookmarks, notes, …). You can backup your bookmarks and notes on the sd-card, and restore them
        later.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        All other settings are self explanatory. If you have problems, you can write a mail (\"Contact?\").
    </string>

    <string name="helpBrowser_title">Browser</string>
    <string name="helpBrowser_text">
        HHS Moodle is shown in this browser. There is a context menu, which opens by long clicking a picture or link.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Swipe:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Swipe down:&lt;/i> reload website.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Create note (pen icon):&lt;/i> A new window will popup, where you can create a note. The title of the website
        is used for the note title. The link is used for the content.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open bookmarks (star icon):&lt;/i> A popup dialog with your bookmark list will open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Add bookmark:&lt;/i> Add the actual website to your bookmark list. A popup dialog where you can edit the title
        of the bookmark will open.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Share bookmark:&lt;/i> You can share the link with every app which is able to receive text
        (SMS, Email,…). You can also make and share screenshots of the whole website (even from the part, which is not on the
        screen). With that you should wait until the whole website is loaded, to avoid problems.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open app directory:&lt;/i> You can open, share, rename und delete files.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Tools:&lt;/i> you can choose between calculate grades, random number generator and course lists.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app. It is highly
        recommended to protect the app with a password against unwanted access.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Help:&lt;/i> Opens the help dialog.
    </string>

    <string name="helpGrade_title">Grade calculation</string>
    <string name="helpGrade_text">
        Moodle always calculates in percentage (0-100%). Grades are always in condition to this scala. If you set the maximal credits
        to 100 you can see this scala. Moodle always calculates with the percent scale, not with the grades.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Maximal credits:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Here you can set the maximal credits for a test. The scored credits (middle column) will be set in relation to the maximal
        reachable credits in percent (left column). In the right column you can see the calculated grade.
    </string>

    <string name="helpRandom_text">

        &lt;b>Choose pupil:&lt;/b>&lt;br>

        If you click on list entry, the course list will open and you can choose a pupil randomly. If you long click the list
        entry a popup menu will be shown. There you can edit the list.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Roll a dice:&lt;/b>&lt;br>

        Choose the menu entry \"random Number\" (Dice icon). A dialog will popup, where you can set a maximum number. Then you
        can press \"OK\" to roll the dice.
    </string>

    <string name="helpCourse_text">

        &lt;b>Create list:&lt;/b>&lt;br>

        &#8226;&lt;i> Create text file:&lt;/i> Create one text file per course. In every line you can write a name. The filename
        should be the course name (e.G..: Course 6a).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Copy to phone:&lt;/i> Copy the text file in the \"HHS_Moodle\" folder on your sd-card.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Load file:&lt;/i> Click on the orange button. In the opening dialog you can choose the copied file.
        A new list entry will be created. Then you can delete the text file.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        If you click on a list entry you can create a note, you can open a menu to edit the list entry.
    </string>

    <string name="helpToDo_activity_text">

        Just enter a new entry and press the \"+\" button. Existing entries can be edited:&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Short click:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        The content of the entry can be edited.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Long click:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        The entry will be deleted. There is a short time period to restore it.
    </string>

    <string name="perm_notShow_title">Permission dialog</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary">Show again: Permission dialog?</string>

</resources>