<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    //License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Used open source projects:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>NotificationNotes&lt;br>
        https://github.com/khuttun/NotificationNotes&lt;br>&lt;br>

        browser&lt;br>
        https://github.com/yoshihiroando/browser&lt;/i>
    </string>


    //Changelog Dialog

    <string name="changelog_text">
        &lt;i>For more informations visit the project site on github:&lt;br>
        https://github.com/scoute-dich/HHSMoodle&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>v 1.0:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226; first release
    </string>


    //Help Dialogs

    <string name="helpBrowser_title">Browser</string>
    <string name="helpBrowser_text">
        HHS Moodle is shown in this webview. A webview displays websites in an app. If you want to be
        logged automatically, you must set your username and your password in the settings. In the webview there is a
        context menu, which opens on long pressing a link or image. You can switch back to the main screen by clicking the toolbar
        or the back arrow.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Swipe:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        Swipe down to reload the website. Swipe right to open previous site, swipe left to move forward.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Menu:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        You can make a new note or a new notification. You can share the actual moodle site as screenshot, or only the link. You can
        also add the actual site as bookmark, to reach it from the main screen and you can directly open the app
        directory.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Save bookmarks:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        To save a bookmark simply click the icon at the toolbar.If you clicked the icon a popup appears. You can now edit the
        title of the bookmark.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Taking screenshots;&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        You can make screenshots of the whole website (even of the part which is outside of your display. Before taking the
        screenshot wait until the website is fully loaded, to ensure that the whole website is captured.</string>


    <string name="helpMain_text">

        &lt;b>My Moodle | Bookmarks&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>The tabs:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        In the left tab you can open your personal Moodle sites and in the middle tab you can see your bookmarks.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Edit bookmarks:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        Long click on a bookmark opens a popup menu. You can set your favorite bookmark
        (You can open the favorite ba clicking the orange \"star button\".), edit the title of the bookmark or
        delete it (at least one bookmark is needed). You can also create a new note or notification.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Notes&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Create notes:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        You can make notes if you click the \"Taking note\" entry in the menu or the pencil icon in the toolbar. If the list does
        not refresh automatically, you can swipe down on the picture above the list.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Working with notes:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        Clicking a list entry opens the note. Long click on an entry opens a popup menu. You can edit the
        note or delete it (at least one note is needed).&lt;br>
        You can also set a notification to the system status bar. A new screen for editing notifications will open.
        The notification will appear again after a reboot.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>
        From the main screen you can create a new note, reach your notifications, open the app directory (where the downloaded
        files will be saved), enter the settings screen or create a new note.</string>


    <string name="helpNotes_text">
        Here you can create new or edit existing notes. After editing click the \"save button\"</string>


    <string name="helpNot_title">Notifications</string>
    <string name="helpNot_text">
        &lt;i>Overview:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        Here your notifications are shown. You can create a new notification from a note, a Moodle site or by clicking the
        \"add icon\". If you activate a notification it will be shown in status bar (even after a reboot). You can delete a
        notification by long clicking.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Edit notification:&lt;/i>&lt;br>
        Here you can create new or edit existing notifications. After editing click the \"save button\".&lt;br>&lt;br>

        You can switch back to the main screen by clicking the toolbar
        or the back arrow.</string>


    <string name="helpSettings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="helpSettings_text">
        To get some settings applied, you must restart the application.</string>


    <string name="dialog_help">
        You can reach a short help dialog on every screen by pressing \"menu -> help\".</string>


    <string name="perm_notShow_title">Permission dialog</string>
    <string name="perm_notShow_title_summary">Show again: Permission dialog?</string>

</resources>